Guide to the Robert A. M. Stern Architects Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records for 1980-1983, Accession 2007-M-094
  - Dushey House, 1982-1984
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 144)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 144)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 32, Box 97)
  - Swid Powell Tableware, 1982-1985
    Job number: 82172
    - Publicity materials (Box 33)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 146)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 33, Box 97)
    - Models (Box 188)
    - Photographs (Box 33)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1A)
  - Schulman Company development, 1982
    Job number: 82296
    Job location: Harrison, NY
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 146)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 97)
  - Ferrin House Garage, 1982-1983
    Job number: 83173
    - Correspondence (Box 33)
    - Job files (Box 33)
    - Construction drawings (Box 146)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 97)
  - Prospect Point office building, 1983-1985
    Job number: 83174
    Job location: La Jolla, CA
    - Correspondence (Box 33–35)
    - Job files (Box 33–35)
    - Publicity materials (Box 35)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 147)
    - Construction drawings (Box 147)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 147)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 35, Box 97)
  - "Dinner at Eight" carpet for Furniture of the 20th Century, 1983
    Job number: 83175
    - Presentation drawings (Box 148)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 97)
  - Warren Peters House interior, 1983
    Job number: 83176
    - Correspondence (Box 36)
    - Job files (Box 36)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 148)
    - Construction drawings (Box 148)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 36, Box 97)
  - Copperflagg residential development, 1983-1989
    Job number: 83177
    - Correspondence (Box 37–40)
    - Job files (Box 37–40)
    - Publicity materials (Box 40)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 148–149)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 148)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 40, Box 149)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 98)
  - Mecox Fields Lot 4: Davin House, 1983
    Job number: 83179
    - Construction drawings (Box 150)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 150)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 99)
  - Schweber Apartment at the Dakota, 1983
    Job number: 83180
    - Correspondence (Box 40)
    - Job files (Box 40)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 150)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 99)
  - Sheehan House [see printed finding aid from RAMSA for more detailed inventory of complex project], 1983-1990
    Job number: 83181
    Job location: Duxbury, MA
    - Correspondence (Box 46, Box 50, Box 52–53, Box 66)
    - Job files (Box 41–44, Box 46–66)
    - Publicity materials (Box 45)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 155)
    - Construction drawings (Box 151–153, Box 156)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 154, Box 156–158)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 156)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 155)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 41, Box 99)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1A)
  - Fusco House, 1983
    Job number: 83182
    Job location: Rumson, NJ
    - Correspondence (Box 67)
    - Job files (Box 67)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 159)
    - Construction drawings (Box 159)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 159)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 67, Box 99)
    - Photographs (Box 67)
  - Ashkenazi House [see printed finding aid from RAMSA for more detailed inventory of complex project], 1983-1989
    Job number: 83184
    - Correspondence (Box 82)
    - Job files (Box 67–82)
    - Publicity materials (Box 82)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 165)
    - Construction drawings (Box 160A–160B)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 161–164, Box 166–168)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 163–164, Box 168)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 161, Box 168)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 165)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 100–103)
    - Photographs (Box 82)
    - Framed artwork (Folder 1A)
  - Fisher Bed, 1982
    Job number: 83185
    - Correspondence (Box 83)
    - Job files (Box 83)
  - Point West Place office building, 1983-1985
    Job number: 83186
    Job location: Framingham, MA
    - Correspondence (Box 84)
    - Job files (Box 84)
    - Publicity materials (Box 84)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 169)
    - Construction drawings (Box 169)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 169)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 169)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 169)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 84, Box 104)
    - Models (Box 187)
  - Shands House, 1983
    Job number: 83187
    Job location: Oldham County, KY
    - Correspondence (Box 85)
    - Job files (Box 85)
    - Publicity materials (Box 85)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 170)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 170)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 104)
    - Framed artwork (Box 1)
  - Meltzer House renovations, 1983
    Job number: 83188
    Job location: Pound Ridge, NY
    - Job files (Box 85)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 171)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 171)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 104)
  - Cherry Creek housing development [Greenhouse Apartments], 1983
    Job number: 83189
    Job location: Denver, CO
    - Job files (Box 85)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 171)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 171)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 171)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 104)
  - Mecox Fields: Lot 2: Vroom House, 1983
    Job number: 83190
    - Construction drawings (Box 171)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 171)
  - Cove Hollow Farm: Lot 14: Kono House, 1980-1984
    Job number: 83191
    - Job files (Box 85)
    - Construction drawings (Box 171)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 171)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 171)
  - Colfax Development: Lot 23: Tuschak House [Beden's Brook], 1983-1986
    Job number: 83192
    - Correspondence (Box 85–86)
    - Job files (Box 85–86)
    - Construction drawings (Box 172)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 172)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 172)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 172)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 86, Box 105)
  - Esses House, 1983-1986
    Job number: 83193
    - Job files (Box 87)
    - Existing conditions/measured drawings (Box 175)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 174)
    - Construction drawings (Box 173)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 174–175)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 174–175)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 174)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 105)
    - Models (Box 187)
  - Knowlton Place, 1983
    Job number: 83194
    Job location: Chappaqua, NY
    - Job files (Box 87)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 176)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 105)
  - Shaw-Walker Showroom, 1983
    Job number: 83196
    - Correspondence (Box 87)
    - Job files (Box 87)
    - Publicity materials (Box 87)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 176)
    - Construction drawings (Box 176)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 176)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 87, Box 105)
  - Anchorage Theater design competition, 1983
    Job number: 83197
    Job location: Anchorage, AK
    - Presentation drawings (Box 176)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 105)
  - Beil Development House, 1983
    Job number: 83198
    - Job files (Box 87)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 105)
  - New Orleans Museum of Art additions design competition, 1983
    Job number: 83199
    Job location: New Orleans, LA
    - Job files (Box 87)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 176)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 105)
  - Goodman House [Lake Agawam], 1983
    Job number: 83200
    Job location: Southampton, NY
    - Correspondence (Box 88–89)
    - Job files (Box 88–89)
    - Publicity materials (Box 89)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 178, Box 180)
    - Construction drawings (Box 177–180)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 179)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 106)
    - Photographs (Box 88–89)
  - Carpet for Paul Goldberger, 1983
    Job number: 83201
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 107)
  - Chappaqua Properties [Fox Hollow Run], 1983
    Job number: 83202
    - Correspondence (Box 90)
    - Job files (Box 90)
    - Publicity materials (Box 90)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 181)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 181)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 181)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 90, Box 107)
  - Ekstract House, 1983-1988
    Job number: 83203
    - Correspondence (Box 90–91)
    - Job files (Box 90–91)
    - Publicity materials (Box 91)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 182)
    - Construction drawings (Box 182)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 182)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 182)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 182)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 182)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 107)
  - Ottinger House, 1983
    Job number: 83205
    Job location: West Tisbury, Martha's Vineyard, MA
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 183)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 183)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 107)
  - Treadway House, 1983-1985
    Job number: 83206
    - Correspondence (Box 91)
    - Job files (Box 91)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 183)
    - Furniture/millwork drawings (Box 183)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 183)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 183)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 107)
  - Schlesinger House
    Job number: 83207
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 184)
    - Construction drawings (Box 183–184)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 183)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 184)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 92, Box 107)
  - Fisher House [Residence at Hardscrabble], 1983-1985
    Job number: 83209
    - Correspondence (Box 91)
    - Job files (Box 91)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 185)
    - Construction drawings (Box 185)
    - Site/landscape drawings (Box 186)
    - Lighting drawings (Box 185)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 185)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 107)
  - Berman House, 1983-1984
    Job number: 83211
    - Correspondence (Box 92)
    - Job files (Box 92–93)
    - Design development/schematic drawings (Box 186)
    - Construction drawings (Box 186)
    - Presentation drawings (Box 186)
    - Sketches/small drawings (Box 92, Box 107)
- Project records for 1985-1986, 1983-2004; Accession 2012-M-058
  General
  "See Also" notes have been supplied by the Creator and some of the projects referred to in these notes have not yet been received.
  - The Stable, 79 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85001), 1983 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    Researchers must receive permission to use these records from Robert A.M. Stern Architects, LLP.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Project Drawings (Box 44)
    - Project Sketches (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - 16 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85002), 1983 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Project Drawings (Box 44)
    - Project Sketches (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - 60 Copperflagg Lane (New York, NY) (85003), 1984 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Project Drawings (Box 44)
    - Project Sketches (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - The Palm House, 63 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85004), 1983 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Project Drawings (Box 44)
    - Project Sketches (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - The Garage, 79 and 1/2 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85005), 1983 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Project Drawings (Box 45)
    - Project Sketches (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - 81 Copperflagg Lane (New York, NY) (85006), 1984 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 45)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 45)
      - Working Drawings (Box 45)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Plans, Sections (Box 133, Folder 6)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 133, Folder 7)
      - Sketches - Pool Pavilion (Box 133, Folder 8)
      - Sketches - Site Plans (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Colfax: Tuschak Interiors (Skillman, NJ) (85008), 1984 - 1985
    See Also: 83192 - Colfax: Tuschak House, Lot 23.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 5 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85011), 1984 - 1986
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 46)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 46)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 134, Folder 11)
      - Working Drawings (Box 46)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Breckenridge Development (Breckenridge, CO) (85012), 1985 - 1986
    See Also: 85038 - Breckenridge Swan Valley Lodge 85039 - Temporary Clubhouse at Swan Valley 85069 - Breckenridge Golf Club 86068 - Breckenridge Legal.
    - Architect/Architect (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Includes correspondence and memoranda.
    - Authorities (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Landscape Architect (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Program Background - Design Guidelines (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Program Background - Related Projects (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Research (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Suite, The Druker Company (Boston, MA) (85019), 1985 - 1986
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Project Drawings (Box 46)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Metairie Park Country Day School (New Orleans, LA) (85020), 1984 - 1985
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Project Drawings (Box 47)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 13)
      This is an unbuilt project.
  - Residence in Dongan Hills (New York, NY) (85022), 1985 - 1989
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85028, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Project Drawings
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 47)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 134, Folder 17)
      - Working Drawings (1) (Box 47)
      - Working Drawings (2) (Box 47)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Plans, Sections (Box 134, Folder 14)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 134, Folder 15)
      - Sketches - Oversized (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Residence at Cove Beach (East Marion, NY) (85023), 1985
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 47)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 48)
      - Site Plans (Box 48)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - House in Cold Spring Harbor (Lloyd's Neck, NY) (85024), 1985
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Project Drawings (Box 48)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Robert A. M. Stern Architects Office (New York, NY) (85025), 1985 - 1986
    - Project File (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Project Drawings
      - Building Department Sheets (Box 48)
      - Design Drawings - Mylar (Box 48)
      - Design Drawings - Vellum (Box 48)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 48)
      - Monograph Drawing (Box 48)
      - Working Drawings (Box 48)
    - Project Sketches (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - The Shops at Primrose Brook (Bernardsville, NJ) (85026), 1985 - 1990
    - Project Files
      - Architect/Client (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Authorities - Building Code Analysis (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Authorities - Morris County, New Jersey (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Authorities - State of New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Authorities - Township of Harding, New Jersey (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Civil (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Contracts (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Geotechnical (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Landscape (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Lighting (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Mechanical (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Memoranda (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - Notes (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Prices (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - Program Background (1) (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Program Background (2) (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Publicity (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Sewage Treatment (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Signage (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Small Drawings (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Specifications (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Structural (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Telephone Booths (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Traffic (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Drawings
      - Civil Engineer (Box 49)
      - Design Drawings - Mylar (Box 49)
      - Design Drawings - Vellum (Box 49)
      - Existing Conditions (Box 49)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 49)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 49)
      - Record Sets (Box 50)
      - Site Planning Set (Box 50)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 135, Folder 25)
      - Working Drawings (Box 50)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Details, Studies (Box 135, Folder 21)
      - Sketches - Elevations, Plans, Perspectives (Box 135, Folder 22)
      - Sketches - Landscape (Box 135, Folder 23)
      - Sketches - Sewage Treatment Plant (Box 135, Folder 24)
  - 27 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85028), 1985 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85036, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Project Drawings (Box 51)
    - Small-Scale Design Drawings (Box 135, Folder 27)
    - Project Sketches (Box 135, Folder 26)
  - Residence Renovation (Green's Farm, CT) (85032), 1985
    - Project File (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Project Drawings (Box 51)
    - Project Sketches (Box 135, Folder 28)
    - Watercolor Rendering - View of Entrance from Driveway (Box 135, Folder 29)
  - Residence in Pottersville (Pottersville, NJ) (85034), 1985 - 1989
    - Project File
      - Architect/Client (Box 3, Folder 48)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Authorities (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Equipment (Box 3, Folder 52)
      - Hardware (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Interiors (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - Landscape (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Lighting (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Mechanical (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Memoranda (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Railing (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Security (Box 3, Folder 60)
      - Site Plan/Survey (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Specifications (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 51)
      - Landscape Architect (Box 51)
      - Monograph Drawing (Box 51)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 51)
      - Working Drawings (Box 52)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Elevations, Plans (Box 135, Folder 30)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 135, Folder 31)
  - Kol Israel Synagogue (New York, NY) (85035), 1985 - 1990
    - Project File
      - Acoustics (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Architect/Client (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Architect/Contractor (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Authorities (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Carpets (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - Community Relations (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Concrete (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Contracts (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Coordination Files (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - Doors (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Field Reports (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - HVAC (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Landscape (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - Lighting (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - Mechanical, Electrical, and Plumbing (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Memoranda (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Metal Work (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Millwork (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Notes (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - Paving (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Plaster (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Research (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Roofing (Box 4, Folder 85)
      - Seating (Box 4, Folder 86)
      - Security System (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Shop Drawing and Submittal Record (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Site Information (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Specifications (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Stonework (Box 4, Folder 92)
      - Structural (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - Temporary Ark (Box 4, Folder 94)
      - Tile Work (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Water Proofing (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - Windows (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - Woodwork (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Project Images (1) (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - Project Images (2) (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - Project Drawings
      - Boring Inspection Sheet (Box 52)
      - Color Studies (Box 52)
      - Design Drawings - Mylar (Box 52)
      - Design Drawings - Vellum (Box 52)
      - MEP Engineer (Box 53)
      - Monograph Drawings (Box 53)
      - Record Sets (Box 53)
      - Small Drawings (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Stone Lettering Drawings (Box 54)
      - Structural Engineer (Box 54)
      - Working Drawings - Part 1 (Box 54)
      - Working Drawings - Part 2 (Box 54)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Casework (Box 135, Folder 36)
      - Small-Scale Design Drawings - Furniture (Box 135, Folder 37)
    - Project Sketches
      - Sketches - Details and Studies (Box 135, Folder 32)
      - Sketches - Elevations, Perspectives (Box 135, Folder 33)
      - Sketches - Interior (Box 135, Folder 34)
      - Sketches - Seating Plans (Box 135, Folder 35)
  - 51 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85036), 1985 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85037, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project File (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Project Drawings (Box 55)
    - Project Sketches (Box 136, Folder 38)
  - 71 Flagg Court (New York, NY) (85037), 1985 - 1987
    See Also: 83177, 85001, 85002, 85003, 85004, 85005, 85006, 85011, 85022, 85028, 85036, 85040, 85051, 85052, 85053, 85057, 85090.
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - Project Drawings (Box 55)
    - Project Sketches (Box 136, Folder 39)
  - Breckenridge Swan Valley Lodge (Breckenridge, CO) (85038), 1985
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - Project Drawings (Box 55)
    - Project Sketches (Box 136, Folder 40)
  - Temporary Clubhouse at Swan Valley (Breckenridge, CO) (85039), 1985
    See Also: 85012 - Breckenridge Development 85038 - Breckenridge Swan Valley Lodge 85069 - Breckenridge Golf Club 86068 - Breckenridge Legal.
    - Project File (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Project Images (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Project Drawings
      - Design Drawings (Box 55)
      - Presentation Drawings (Box 55)
      - Working Drawings (Box 55)
    - Project Sketches (Box 136, Folder 41)
  - 24 Copperflagg Lane (New York, NY) (85040), Project Sketches, 1985 (Box 136, Folder 42)